const animals = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "What name is given to an adult female sheep?",
        answer: "ewe",
        hint: "Three letter palindrome"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "Which large marine mammals are sometimes referred to as 'sea cows'?",
        answer: "manatees",
        hint: "-----"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "Which country is the natural habitat and home of lemurs?",
        answer: "madagascar",
        hint: "Island of the coast of Africa"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Name the slowest animal in the world.",
        answer: "sloth",
        hint: "One of the seven deadly sins"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "All six legs of an ant are attach to which body part?",
        answer: "thorax",
        hint: "This is the middle part of the ant"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "Which animal never sleeps?",
        answer: "bullfrog",
        hint: "Large amphibian native to North America"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Which animal has the longest lifespan?",
        answer: "bowhead whale",
        hint: "Lives in the arctic and sub arctic waters"
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "What type of animal is a Mexican Hairless?",
        answer: "dog",
        hint: "Commonly referred to as man's best friend"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "How many legs does a lobster have?",
        answer: "10",
        hint: "Between 6 and 12"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "What is a group of giraffes known as?",
        answer: "tower",
        hint: "A word for a tall man made object for looking out from"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "What gives the flamingo it's distinctive pink/orange colour?",
        answer: "algea",
        hint: "A certain type of ( ) they eat"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "What do butterflies use their proboscis for?",
        answer: "Eating",
        hint: "Collecting nectar is a form of ( ) for them"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "Which animal has a Spanish name which when translated into English means 'little armoured one'?",
        answer: "armadillo",
        hint: "Typically found in Central and south America"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "What part of the world is the Capybara native to?",
        answer: "south america",
        hint: "The word Capybara is from Spanish and Portuguese origins"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "What do squids, snails and oysters have in common?",
        answer: "they are molluscs",
        hint: "There are around 85,000 decendents of this animal"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "Which flightless bird is the emblem of New Zealand?",
        answer: "kiwi",
        hint: "This animal is a slang term for New Zealanders"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "Which creature has the largest brain in proportion to its body?",
        answer: "ant",
        hint: "Think small"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "Which bird can fly backwards?",
        answer: "hummingbird",
        hint: "Famous for its abillity to hover in place to collect nectar"
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: "What substance  are shark skeletons made of?",
        answer: "cartilage",
        hint: "Also found in the human nose and ears"
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: "Which is the only venomous snake native to the UK?",
        answer: "adder",
        hint: "Usually found in woodland and heathland"
    }

]

export default animals;